Office of Publications Records UA012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Students, 1960 -- 2005; 1963 -- 2002; UA012.002; 3.7 Linear Feet
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing.
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00033 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (class).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00034 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (computer).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00035 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (grad).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00039 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (group).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00043 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00047 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00048 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00049 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00050 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00051 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (helping).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00052 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (rollerblading).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00053 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (saxophone).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00054 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (small group).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00055 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00056 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00057 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00058 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00059 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (study group).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00060 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00061 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (studying).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00062 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00063 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (suitcase).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00064 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00065 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (supplies).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00066 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00067 (Box 7)
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00068 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (swimming).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00069 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (technology).
  - Admissions May 1998 R. Howard, UA012.002.007.00070 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (tennis).
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00071 (Box 7)
    This folder contains slides of students, faculty, and Tufts scenery.
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00072 (Box 7)
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00073 (Box 7)
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00074 (Box 7)
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00075 (Box 7)
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00076 (Box 7)
  - Admission Slideshow, 1980; UA012.002.007.00077 (Box 7)
  - Campus, 1990 -- 1991; UA012.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of academic quad, West hall
  - Campus Scenes, 1980; UA012.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students conversing, campus scenes. Date is approximate
  - Campus Scenes, classes, students, 1961; UA012.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students drama, winter scenes, Eaton, classes, students
  - Campus Scenes, classes, students, 1961; UA012.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students academic quad, technology, lake, classes, winter scene
  - Campus Scenes, classes, students, 1961; UA012.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students, drama, technology, lake, classes, winter scene
  - Students- early sixties, 1960; UA012.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students. Date is approximate
  - Campus scenes - early sixties, 1960; UA012.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students, winter scenes, lake, Ballou, Eaton, Charmicael. Date is approximate
  - Campus scenes - early sixties, 1960; UA012.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of academic quad, proffessor, students, Cohen, fraternity, general campus scenes. Date is approximate
  - Campus scenes - early sixties, 1960; UA012.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of professor, classroom, Cohen, interior Goddard, general campus scenes. Date is approximate
  - Campus scenes - early sixties, 1961; UA012.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of Goddard, Eaton, Labratory, library, general campus, Fletcher, Miller, classroom
  - Campus scenes - students, music, 1961; UA012.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of Bowen gate, library, general campus with students
  - Campus scenes - students, music, 1961; UA012.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of students playing instruments, classroom, conductor
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of student with guitar, general campus, sculpture, street signes, gates, moldings
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of West, Miller, Olin, gate, stairs, flyers
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of sculpture, Charmicael, Chemistry building, bench with students, tennis courts, other building
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of students and library court, bike rack
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of students talking, on library roof, and steps of Eaton
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of students walking, on terrace, on bench, student wearing Tufts shirt, flower
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of crazy scientist, bike rack, students on grass, academic quad, Ballou, flowers, Goddard, Tisch, Tisch roof
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of students on academic quad, Tisch roof
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of student on bench, flowers, academic quad/West, overhang of Ballou, Olin, Barnum, Barnum and students
  - Campus shots - Prospective students, Mark Morelli, 1997; UA012.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of students on Tisch roof
  - Classroom, 1985; UA012.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes. Date is approximate
  - Classroom, 1985; UA012.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Classroom, 1985; UA012.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
    This folder contains negatives of classroom scenes. Date is approximate
  - Dorm Life, 1980; UA012.002.008.00026 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of dorm interiors, students studying, talking. Date is approximate
  - EMI students in classes, 1996; UA012.002.008.00027 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of classroom scenes
  - Fletcher Students, 1996; UA012.002.008.00028 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of Woman outside of Fletcher
  - Fletcher Students, 1996; UA012.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students, 1995; UA012.002.008.00030 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of man and woman in library. Date is approximate
  - Fletcher Students: Brian Casa Cianca and Christine Samuel, 1995; UA012.002.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Brian Casa Cianca and Christine Samuel, 1995; UA012.002.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Brian Casa Cianca and Christine Samuel, 1995; UA012.002.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Camelia Mazzard, 1995; UA012.002.008.00034 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of woman in front of map. Date is approximate
  - Fletcher Students: Camelia Mazzard, 1995; UA012.002.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Camelia Mazzard, 1995; UA012.002.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Camelia Mazzard, 1995; UA012.002.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Camelia Mazzard, 1995; UA012.002.008.00038 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of woman in front of map (and one of Brian Casa Bianca and Christine Samuel). Date is approximate
  - Fletcher Students: Candice Lun, 1996; UA012.002.008.00039 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of woman in front of books
  - Fletcher Students: Greg Unich, 1995; UA012.002.008.00040 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of man on Fletcher blacony. Date is approximate
  - Fletcher Students: Greg Unich, 1995; UA012.002.008.00041 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Greg Unich, 1995; UA012.002.008.00042 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of man on Fletcher blacony (and one of other man). Date is approximate
  - Fletcher Students: Greg Unich, 1995; UA012.002.008.00043 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Greg Unich, 1995; UA012.002.008.00044 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Greg Unich, 1995; UA012.002.008.00045 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Meg McAuciffe, 1995; UA012.002.008.00046 (Box 8)
    This folder contains slides of woman in hallway. Date is approximate
  - Fletcher Students: Meg McAuciffe, 1995; UA012.002.008.00047 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Meg McAuciffe, 1995; UA012.002.008.00048 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students: Meg McAuciffe, 1995; UA012.002.008.00049 (Box 8)
  - Fletcher Students - Rom Gallegos, 1996; UA012.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Rom Gallegos, 1996; UA012.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Rom Gallegos, 1996; UA012.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sean Liab, 1996; UA012.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sean Liab, 1996; UA012.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sebastian Tiger, 1996; UA012.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sophie Clemens, 1996; UA012.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Fletcher Students - Sophie Clemens, 1996; UA012.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Group study and Packard Hall, 1985; UA012.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
    Slides show small groups of students studying, students conversing, students in front of Packard Hall, single student portraits, and one slide depicts a group playing basketball.
  - GSAS Students, 1996; UA012.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
    Slides show students outside of GSAS building on 112 Packard Ave.
  - GSAS Students, 1996; UA012.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
    Date is approximate. Slides show students outside of GSAS building on 112 Packard Ave.
  - GSAS Students (Best), 1996; UA012.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Azalea, Drama, UA012.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
    Show student, Azalea, in theater.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Azalea, Drama, UA012.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - girl with soccer ball, UA012.002.009.00021 (Box 9)
    Show student posed outside with soccer ball.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Lucy Mends, UA012.002.009.00022 (Box 9)
    Show student, Lucy Mends, next to pillars, possible in front of Ballou Hall.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Lucy Mends, UA012.002.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Michelle, Engineer, UA012.002.009.00024 (Box 9)
    Show engineering student, Michelle, outside reading a book.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Michelle, Engineer, UA012.002.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Michelle, Engineer, UA012.002.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Nephis, UA012.002.009.00027 (Box 9)
    Show student, Nephis against a backdrop of bricks.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Nephis, UA012.002.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Swimmi, UA012.002.009.00029 (Box 9)
    Show student, Swimmi, studying.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Swimmi, UA012.002.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Swimmi, UA012.002.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Interview, 1996 -- 1997; UA012.002.009.00032 (Box 9)
    Show students during a meeting or interview, maybe in admissions office.
  - Large Groups, 1989; UA012.002.009.00033 (Box 9)
    Slides show large group of students posed on a bench outside.
  - Large Groups, 1981 -- 1996; UA012.002.009.00034 (Box 9)
    Pictures show large groups of students outside, some could depict a protest or a speech, others might be a sports came. Also contains slides of students in cafeteria, students conversing, one group photograph, and one portrait.
  - Library Scenes, 1995; UA012.002.009.00035 (Box 9)
    Date is approximate. Shots of students studying in the library.
  - Kids Modeling, 1995; UA012.002.009.00036 (Box 9)
    Some slides of children, but others of Tufts memorabilia, students posing next to cannon, student next to pillars, students next to small elephant statue and students conversing outside
  - Medford students on campus, 1965 -- 1985; UA012.002.009.00037 (Box 9)
    Mostly outdoor scenes of students walking, studying and relaxing, some in summer, some with snow. One shot of dining, and one of children on a playground.
  - Medford students on campus, 1981 -- 1995; UA012.002.009.00038 (Box 9)
    Individual portraits, students conversing and studying, outdoor and indoor, women carrying white flowers, and a dorm group playing Twister.
  - Individual Student Portraits 1998 - Lucy Mends, UA012.002.009.00039 (Box 9)
    slide (photograph)
  - Medford campus outdoor scenes, 1993; UA012.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
    Students posed by Bowen Gate.
  - Medford campus outdoor scenes, 1993; UA012.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
    Students posed by Bowen Gate. Students studying on lawn. Students in front of Ballou Hall.
  - Medford campus - snow, 1977; UA012.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
    Students on campus in the snow.
  - Medford campus - students, 1987 -- 1994; UA012.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
    Dates are approximate. Mostly shots of students walking around campus. Some posed groups. Some in classrooms.
  - Medford students, 1990; UA012.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
    Dates are approximate. Internegatives of meeting in International Center, student using computer, student studying in front of tree, and students working on a group project.
  - Medford students on campus, 1993 -- 1997; UA012.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
    Some shots of grass, pillars, and president's house. Also shots of students lying in a circle, students in front of Ballou Hall, and students walking around campus.
  - Medford students on campus, 1985 -- 1990; UA012.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
    Individual portraits of students inside and outside, a couple of group shots, and two pictures of dining.
  - Misc. Students, 1980 -- 1990; UA012.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
    Students playing frisbee, outdoor scenes, including shot of student on Tisch roof.
  - Outdoors, 1980 -- 1990; UA012.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
    Students outsidein the sun, on Tisch roof garden, outdoor classes, lawn in front of Ballou Hall.
  - Outdoor class, 1986 -- 1994; UA012.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
    Students in classes being conducted outside.
  - Outdoor class, 1980 -- 1994; UA012.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Outdoor class scenes, 1994; UA012.002.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Outdoor educational, 1994; UA012.002.010.00013 (Box 10)
    Students in classes being conducted outside. Students talking to professors outside. Students studying outside.
  - Outdoor educational, 1994; UA012.002.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Outdoor educational, 1994; UA012.002.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Outdoor social scenes, 1994; UA012.002.010.00016 (Box 10)
    Students in classes being conducted outside. Students chatting and student playing guitar.
  - Outdoor class scenes, 1994; UA012.002.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - [Outdoor Scenes], 1994; UA012.002.010.00018 (Box 10)
    Students in classes being conducted outside. Students walking past elephant statue in front of Barnum Hall. Students on outdoor deck.
  - [Outdoor Scenes], 1994; UA012.002.010.00019 (Box 10)
    Students walking around campus. One student staring pensively into a swamp.
  - [Outdoor Scenes], 1994; UA012.002.010.00020 (Box 10)
    Students walking and sitting around campus.
  - Outdoor studying, 1987 -- 1990; UA012.002.010.00021 (Box 10)
    Single students reading outside.
  - Posed classroom, 2002; UA012.002.010.00022 (Box 10)
    Single students posed in otherwise empty classrooms. One appears to be a literature student, the other an engineering student.
  - Scenes with children, 1995; UA012.002.010.00023 (Box 10)
    Students with children, perhaps taken at the Eliot-Pearson School. Other pictures of posed groups, single student portraits, and one student using the library.
  - Small groups, 1988 -- 1989; UA012.002.010.00024 (Box 10)
    Groups sitting on benches
  - Small groups, 1990 -- 1995; UA012.002.010.00025 (Box 10)
    Posed groups of students.
  - Small groups, 1990 -- 1993; UA012.002.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - Small groups, 1988 -- 1995; UA012.002.010.00028 (Box 10)
    Posed groups of students relaxing outside.
  - Small groups, 1985 -- 1989; UA012.002.010.00029 (Box 10)
    Groups of students relaxing outside. One shot of group playing volleyball.
  - Small groups, 1987 -- 1994; UA012.002.010.00030 (Box 10)
    Dorm scenes, students socializing in classrooms, students talking in labs, students talking outside.
  - Students in class, 1986 -- 1988; UA012.002.010.00031 (Box 10)
    Students studying, talking to faculty, or in classrooms.
  - Students - Ballou Hall, 1988 -- 1989; UA012.002.010.00032 (Box 10)
    Students sitting in front of Ballou.
  - Students - Ballou Hall, 1989; UA012.002.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Students - Medford Campus, 1986 -- 1990; UA012.002.010.00034 (Box 10)
    Students sitting outside.
  - Students, 1961; UA012.002.010.00035 (Box 10)
    Scenes in library, woman playing clarinet, technology.
  - Students, 1961; UA012.002.010.00036 (Box 10)
    Scenes in lab, classroom, outside.
  - Students, 1961; UA012.002.010.00037 (Box 10)
    Scenes in classroom, individual portraits.
  - Students, 1961; UA012.002.010.00038 (Box 10)
    Scenes in classroom, outside.
  - Students, 1961; UA012.002.010.00039 (Box 10)
    Scenes in classrooms, students with microscopes, using early technology, meeting scenes.
  - Students, 1961; UA012.002.010.00040 (Box 10)
    Scenes in classrooms, students with microscopes, using early technology, engineering, students in orchestra.
  - Study - in class, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.002.010.00041 (Box 10)
    Students in classroom settings.
  - Summer, 1994; UA012.002.010.00042 (Box 10)
    Students in sunglasses and students talking to professors in library.
  - Summer, 1991; UA012.002.010.00043 (Box 10)
    Groups of students in front of Ballou Hall and on Tisch roof garden. Also posed shot of students on bench.
  - Summer, 1990 -- 1991; UA012.002.010.00044 (Box 10)
    Groups of students enjoying summer weather in posed groups.
  - Tisch library, 1969 -- 1997; UA012.002.010.00045 (Box 10)
    Students using library. Not always Tisch, some photos outdate Tisch.
  - Tufts - campus, classes, 1961; UA012.002.010.00046 (Box 10)
    Photos of theater productions, Eliot Pearson scenes, student dining, football, microscopes, general campus scenes, and art class.
  - Tufts campus scenes, 1961; UA012.002.010.00047 (Box 10)
    Photos ofstudent dining, football, and general campus scenes.
  - WMJ Keller Finer Yearbooks, 1960; UA012.002.010.00048 (Box 10)
    Date is approximate. Three photographs of football games, and one of a couple sitting on campus.
  - WMJ Keller Finer Yearbooks, 1960; UA012.002.010.00049 (Box 10)
    Date is approximate. Two photographs of students at a bar. One photograph of basketball, one of football.
  - WMJ Keller Finer Yearbooks, 1960; UA012.002.010.00050 (Box 10)
    Date is approximate. Two photographs of students at commencement. One photograph of luau-like party, one of outdoor class.
  - Students - Ballou Hall, 1989; UA012.002.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - Students in fall, 1980 -- 1987; UA012.002.023.00013 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
  - Students outside, 1986 -- 1998; UA012.002.023.00014 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains images of students chattings, looking at bulletin boards, and walking around campus.
  - Students outside, 1984 -- 1998; UA012.002.023.00015 (Box UA012 Shared 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains images of students biking, Ballou Hall, and Tisch steps.
- Faculty and Staff, 1960 -- 2002; 1963 -- 2002; UA012.003; 2.9 Linear Feet; 2 Digital Object(s)